Greetings new employee! Thank you for willingly, or unwillingly, applying to work at the ground-breaking facilities of the Sun Corporation!
If you have been acquired due to your debt, you will remain with us until it has been decided it is repaid.
Formed during the 1980s sun expeditions, the Sun Corporation is the worldwide leader in energy production, this energy made us the perfect partner for
project 'Divine', where our advanced power grid is used to assist in the suppression of otherworldly forces.
Using our patented defence systems, you'll be working to keep your assigned sector online.
Since the first reported instance of debris falling in [redacted] we have succeeded at stopping [redacted] breaches and we are relying on YOU to continue our success
You have automatically been assigned a manager and your initiation begins immediately.
Find your nearest hoist way to take you to your mandatory training sessions.
The future of yourself, and the company depends on your success.
We hope you have an enjoyable stay with the Sun Corporation.